<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Loko</title>
    <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Loko</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://nmin11.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Romantic Vibes in Hakodate</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/14-hakodate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/14-hakodate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After a sunny stay in Sendai, I took the Shinkansen for two and a half hours and arrived in Hakodate, greeted by cloudy skies and a biting, cold sea breeze.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;For the first time during my journey across Japan, I felt the chill of winter.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;In front of Kanemori Red Brick Warehouse&#34; src=&#34;https://nmin11.github.io/jr-travel/hakodate-1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;How could this be?&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Still, with only a short 1-night, 2-day itinerary in Hakodate, there was no time to lose.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I checked into my hotel and quickly set out, clutching my umbrella tightly.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Having traveled across Japan for 20 days, I was already well-acquainted with unpredictable weather.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Quiet Autumn Journey to Sendai</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/13-sendai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/13-sendai/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After leaving behind Tokyo&amp;rsquo;s consistently sunny weather, I arrived in Sendai, only to be greeted by torrential rain.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;In front of Sendai Station&#34; src=&#34;https://nmin11.github.io/jr-travel/sendai-1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the first day in Sendai, I wanted to explore the city, but since it was already late, the sightseeing loop bus that connects the main attractions had stopped operating.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;So, after taking a short rest at the hotel, I headed out for a casual walk around the city.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A City Where Goals and Plans Matter: Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/12-tokyo/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/12-tokyo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tokyo felt overwhelming to me.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;It’s such a vast city with so much to do and see.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;It was also my first time visiting Tokyo, so I struggled with how to fit my plans into the train travel theme.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;So, I decided to follow a beginner’s guide to Tokyo that I found on YouTube.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;After doing some research, I settled on key spots like Roppongi, Shinjuku, Ueno, Shibuya, and Akihabara.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I planned to use the Yamanote Line, Tokyo’s circular JR line, to get around these spots while making the most of my JR Pass.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The JR Pass, which had been useful for long-distance Shinkansen rides, proved to be just as valuable in navigating the city.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Missing Mount Fuji in Fujinomiya</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/11-fujinomiya/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/11-fujinomiya/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Following my Kyoto trip, the Fujinomiya leg of my journey was another disappointment.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;During this train adventure, I had hoped to experience Japan&amp;rsquo;s iconic landmark, Mount Fuji.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Since Fuji trekking is only possible from July to September, my plan was to enjoy views of the mountain from a reasonable distance while exploring Fujinomiya.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;However, it rained nonstop during my stay, and I couldn’t catch even a glimpse of Mount Fuji.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;On top of that, my cold worsened, leaving me with little energy to explore.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;In the end, this leg of the journey turned into more of a resting stop.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Failed Journey Through Kyoto&#39;s Heart</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/10-kyoto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/10-kyoto/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;While Amanohashidate is a beautiful attraction located in Kyoto Prefecture, when people say they’ve visited “Kyoto,” they usually mean Kyoto City and its surrounding areas.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;However, in my case, I initially planned to spend two nights in Kyoto but ended up dedicating one of those nights to Arashiyama.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This left my Kyoto City itinerary feeling rushed and incomplete.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/W4Xunk7CA5E?autoplay=0&amp;controls=1&amp;end=0&amp;loop=0&amp;mute=0&amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&#xA;      &gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In the afternoon, I traveled back to Kyoto from Amanohashidate and immediately headed to &lt;strong&gt;Arashiyama&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;As a destination that has served as a retreat for nobles since the Heian period, Arashiyama offers plenty to see and provides a perfect environment for a leisurely stroll.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Most Beautiful Place in Japan: Amanohashidate</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/9-amanohashidate/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/9-amanohashidate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;After finishing my trip in Osaka, my next destination was Kyoto.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Before exploring Kyoto City itself, I decided to visit a breathtaking spot in Kyoto Prefecture.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Although I had planned this visit in advance, I found myself hesitating, asking, &lt;em&gt;“Am I really going there?”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Because it’s located at the northernmost tip of Kansai, it was quite far.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;In the end, my desire to see one of Japan&amp;rsquo;s three most scenic views and experience a small-town atmosphere won me over, and I headed to &lt;strong&gt;Amanohashidate&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Humble Osaka Journey</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/8-osaka/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/8-osaka/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;osakas-okonomiyaki-which-ones-better&#34;&gt;Osaka’s Okonomiyaki: Which One&amp;rsquo;s Better?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After returning from Nara in the evening, I found myself back in Osaka with a mission: to try Kansai-style &lt;strong&gt;okonomiyaki&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I wanted to experience firsthand how it differs from the Hiroshima-style.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Surprisingly, despite Hiroshima&amp;rsquo;s abundance of okonomiyaki restaurants, finding a specialized okonomiyaki spot in Osaka’s Dotonbori wasn’t as easy as I thought.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The sheer variety of eateries made it harder to settle on one.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;After wandering for about an hour, I finally found a place.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nara: A Place Fulfilled by Deer</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/7-nara/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/7-nara/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;My stay in Osaka was booked for three nights and four days.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;After arriving in Osaka from Kobe, I had no plans that evening and simply enjoyed a good night’s rest.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The following morning, I set out for &lt;strong&gt;Nara&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/-wZdd5eRNVQ?autoplay=0&amp;controls=1&amp;end=0&amp;loop=0&amp;mute=0&amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&#xA;      &gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In South Korea, deer are rare to encounter.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;But in Nara, they are everywhere—far surpassing the numbers I saw in Miyajima, Hiroshima.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;No matter where you go in Nara Park, you’ll find deer strolling around, utterly unafraid of people.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Charming City of Kobe</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/6-kobe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/6-kobe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;kobe-a-city-of-beautiful-nightscapes&#34;&gt;Kobe, a City of Beautiful Nightscapes&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After traveling from Himeji to Kobe and checking into my accommodation, it was already evening.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Originally, I had considered visiting &lt;strong&gt;Rokko Garden Terrace&lt;/strong&gt; in the evening, but due to time constraints, I decided to head to &lt;strong&gt;Harborland&lt;/strong&gt; instead.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Harborland&#34; src=&#34;https://nmin11.github.io/jr-travel/kobe-1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Although I couldn’t view the city from an observatory, the night atmosphere at Harborland was just as enjoyable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;    &#xA;    &lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/6jtffWPCtAY?autoplay=0&amp;controls=1&amp;end=0&amp;loop=0&amp;mute=0&amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&#xA;      &gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kobe certainly had its share of tourists, but there seemed to be an even greater number of locals.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This gave the area a lively, authentic vibe, with many restaurants catering primarily to residents.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The White Egret Castle of Himeji</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/5-himeji/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/5-himeji/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;himeji-castle-the-elegant-white-egret&#34;&gt;Himeji Castle: The Elegant White Egret&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I spent about half a day in Himeji.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;For many travelers, Himeji isn’t usually the main destination.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Instead, it’s often a stopover during extended trips around the Kansai region.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;For me, traveling by Shinkansen from Kagoshima to Sapporo, stopping in Himeji was convenient.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;So, I decided to visit one of Japan’s most iconic landmarks, the elegant white castle, &lt;strong&gt;Himeji Castle&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Entrance to Himeji Castle&#34; src=&#34;https://nmin11.github.io/jr-travel/himeji-1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiroshima: As Vast as Its Name</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/4-hiroshima/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/4-hiroshima/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Although my schedule for Hiroshima spanned three days and two nights, I arrived late on the first evening and left early the last morning for Himeji.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This meant I had only one full day to explore Hiroshima.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Looking back, though, it was a day packed with memorable experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-first-encounter-with-okonomiyaki&#34;&gt;My First Encounter with Okonomiyaki&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I arrived on the first evening, it was already dark outside, but I couldn’t let the day end without ticking off one of my plans: &lt;strong&gt;okonomiyaki&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Hiroshima-style okonomiyaki is quite different from the Kansai version, and I was determined to try both during this trip.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;That’s why I made my way to &lt;strong&gt;Okonomimura&lt;/strong&gt;, a building packed with okonomiyaki specialty restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recharging in Fukuoka</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/3-fukuoka/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/3-fukuoka/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-moment-to-recharge&#34;&gt;A Moment to Recharge&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Hakata Station&#34; src=&#34;https://nmin11.github.io/jr-travel/fukuoka-1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Back at the familiar Hakata Station in Fukuoka.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Before setting off to explore new destinations, I decided to take some time to recharge until the following morning.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Originally, I came with the idea of a backpacking trip, but my shoulders were already feeling the strain.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Continuing this long journey with just a backpack seemed unsustainable.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Having ridden the Shinkansen a few times, I noticed that many other travelers and Japanese commuters used rolling suitcases. Since the Shinkansen was my main mode of transportation, I decided to follow their style.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This trip wasn’t so much a “backpacking journey” as it was a “train journey.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warm Scenes of Kagoshima</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/2-kagoshima/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/2-kagoshima/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;sengan-en-the-satsuma-garden&#34;&gt;Sengan-en, the Satsuma Garden&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After returning to Kagoshima from Yakushima late in the evening, I spent some time organizing my wet clothes and shoes.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The next morning, I had only about half a day to explore Kagoshima for the last time.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Even within that short span, I had a few places to visit: Shiroyama Observatory, Sengan-en, and Sakurajima.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Craving a peaceful morning walk, I decided to head to &lt;strong&gt;Sengan-en&lt;/strong&gt; first.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lush and Verdant Ancient Forests of Yakushima</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/1-yakushima/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/1-yakushima/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;journey-to-yakushima&#34;&gt;Journey to Yakushima&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the first day of my trip, I took a morning flight to Fukuoka, exchanged my physical JR Pass, and stayed in Fukuoka for the day.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The plan was to activate the JR Pass on the second day to maximize its use.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;So, in a way, my first day wasn’t about heading straight to Yakushima but rather a &lt;strong&gt;preview of Fukuoka&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Hakata Station&#34; src=&#34;https://nmin11.github.io/jr-travel/yakushima-1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During the day, I did some light shopping around Hakata Station and enjoyed Fukuoka’s nightlife, exploring Canal City and Nakasu in the evening.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Yakushima to Sapporo: A Nationwide Train Journey Across Japan</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/essay/1-jr-travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/essay/1-jr-travel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;time-to-go&#34;&gt;Time to Go!&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When my resignation was finalized in August, the thought of traveling began to bubble up in my mind.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;From 2020, I had spent two years preparing to transition into a developer role, followed by another two years working as a developer—during which I hadn&amp;rsquo;t traveled at all.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;As my career came to a pause, I felt an urge to rethink my future: how I wanted to live and what kind of work I wanted to pursue.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Instead of rushing forward blindly, I wanted to stop for a moment and recalibrate the direction of my life.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Surely, travel is the best way to go about it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Major GC Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/4-major-gc-algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/4-major-gc-algorithms/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This article was written with the intention of studying major GC algorithms more deeply while participating in the &amp;lsquo;Optimizing Java&amp;rsquo; study.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;serial-gc&#34;&gt;Serial GC&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://github.com/nmin11/blog/assets/75058239/2a864abb-d0f9-4371-a7ea-e86db324af71&#34; width=300&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;The simplest GC implementation&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Only one thread performs GC after Stop-The-World (STW)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Uses the mark-sweep-compact algorithm&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Not suitable for multi-threaded environments&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;❖ Enable Serial GC flag&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; style=&#34;color:#f8f8f2;background-color:#282a36;-moz-tab-size:4;-o-tab-size:4;tab-size:4;&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-bash&#34; data-lang=&#34;bash&#34;&gt;&lt;span style=&#34;display:flex;&#34;&gt;&lt;span&gt;java -XX:+UseSerialGC&#xA;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;parallel-gc&#34;&gt;Parallel GC&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;img src=&#34;https://github.com/nmin11/blog/assets/75058239/fbf491b0-e50e-4c8d-91c1-2908a363b0d1&#34; width=400&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Default GC from Java 5 to 8&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Also known as the &lt;em&gt;Throughput Collector&lt;/em&gt; as it maximizes GC throughput&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Advantageous algorithm when there is sufficient memory space and a high number of cores&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Flags can be used to configure parameters such as the maximum number of threads, maximum pause time, and GC execution time ratio&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;-XX:ParallelGCThreads=&amp;lt;N&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;-XX:MaxGCPauseMillis=&amp;lt;N&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;code&gt;-XX:GCTimeRatio=&amp;lt;N&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;❖ Enable Parallel GC flag&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWS CDK is not a silver bullet</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/3-aws-cdk-is-not-a-silver-bullet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/3-aws-cdk-is-not-a-silver-bullet/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;tldr-generated-by-notion-ai&#34;&gt;TL;DR (Generated by Notion AI)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While AWS CDK (Cloud Development Kit) has become a popular choice for infrastructure-as-code (IaC) development, it is important to note that it is not a silver bullet solution for all use cases.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Firstly, AWS CDK may not be the best choice for smaller projects or simple infrastructure setups that do not require a lot of customization. In such cases, using a simpler IaC tool or even writing code directly in the AWS console may be more efficient.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious S3 Access Denied Error</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/2-s3-access-denied-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/2-s3-access-denied-error/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;how-i-discovered-the-error&#34;&gt;How I discovered the error&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I actually encountered the same error twice.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Neither error occurred in the course of work, but both occurred on the side projects that I had implemented a feature to test work-related functionality.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;What I implemented was a &lt;strong&gt;Lambda function that triggered by S3 object created event.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;These Lambda functions had a common logic: &lt;strong&gt;get the object&amp;rsquo;s key name from the received event, and look up the object information again via that key name.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;However, my Lambda functions returned an Access Denied error.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Even though my lambda functions had enough permission to run &lt;code&gt;GetObject&lt;/code&gt; from that bucket!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Make tech blog with Github Pages</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/1-make-tech-blog-with-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/1-make-tech-blog-with-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;0-what-is-github-pages&#34;&gt;0. What is Github Pages?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Github Pages is a useful tool that allows us to create our own website for free without a server or DB.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;It is widely used not only for blogs but also for resumes, portfolios, official documents, galleries, and archives.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;(Especially, many developer create portfolio with Github Pages.)&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I also chose Github Pages because I wanted to create a new tech blog!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://pages.github.com&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;Github Pages&lt;/a&gt;&#xA;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;1-why-hugo&#34;&gt;1. Why Hugo?&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In order to create Github Pages, we need to use &lt;strong&gt;Static Site Generator&lt;/strong&gt;, which create static website.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I checked the &lt;a href=&#34;https://ossinsight.io/collections/static-site-generator/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;ranking&lt;/a&gt;&#xA; without hesitation.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Hugo, which I chose from the ranking table, was ranked 6th as of February 2023, indicating that it is a very popular tool.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;In addition, there were many blog posts in Korean language that show how to deploy Github Pages using Hugo, and it looked really easy and simple.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;As Hugo supported various themes, I thought I just needed to choose a theme and change it to suit my taste.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;profile-row&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;profile-column&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;img class=&#34;profile-image&#34; src=&#34;https://nmin11.github.io/about-profile.jpg&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;profile_column&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;h3&gt;Namgung Min&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;contact-info&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p&gt;Email: nmin1124@gmail.com&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p&gt;Github: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/nmin11&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;https://github.com/nmin11&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;im-namgung-min-a-2nd-year-backend-developer&#34;&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Namgung Min, a 2nd-year backend developer.&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;-i-want-to-experience-growing-with-the-company&#34;&gt;🌱 I want to experience growing with the company.&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I believe that meaningful growth can be achieved when we are aligned with the company&amp;rsquo;s vision. I want to experience growing with the company by working actively based on empathy for the business.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;-i-believe-that-good-colleagues-are-the-best-form-of-wellbeing&#34;&gt;🙌 I believe that good colleagues are the best form of wellbeing.&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I want to work with good colleagues and learn from each other&amp;rsquo;s strengths and grow together. I want to enjoy working with colleagues based on open and honest communication.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
