<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jr-Travels on Loko</title>
    <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jr-Travels on Loko</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hiroshima: As Vast as Its Name</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/4-hiroshima/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/4-hiroshima/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Although my schedule for Hiroshima spanned three days and two nights, I arrived late on the first evening and left early the last morning for Himeji.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This meant I had only one full day to explore Hiroshima.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Looking back, though, it was a day packed with memorable experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-first-encounter-with-okonomiyaki&#34;&gt;My First Encounter with Okonomiyaki&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I arrived on the first evening, it was already dark outside, but I couldn’t let the day end without ticking off one of my plans: &lt;strong&gt;okonomiyaki&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Hiroshima-style okonomiyaki is quite different from the Kansai version, and I was determined to try both during this trip.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;That’s why I made my way to &lt;strong&gt;Okonomimura&lt;/strong&gt;, a building packed with okonomiyaki specialty restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recharging in Fukuoka</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/3-fukuoka/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/3-fukuoka/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-moment-to-recharge&#34;&gt;A Moment to Recharge&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Hakata Station&#34; src=&#34;https://nmin11.github.io/jr-travel/fukuoka-1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Back at the familiar Hakata Station in Fukuoka.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Before setting off to explore new destinations, I decided to take some time to recharge until the following morning.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Originally, I came with the idea of a backpacking trip, but my shoulders were already feeling the strain.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Continuing this long journey with just a backpack seemed unsustainable.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Having ridden the Shinkansen a few times, I noticed that many other travelers and Japanese commuters used rolling suitcases. Since the Shinkansen was my main mode of transportation, I decided to follow their style.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;This trip wasn’t so much a “backpacking journey” as it was a “train journey.”&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Warm Scenes of Kagoshima</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/2-kagoshima/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/2-kagoshima/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;sengan-en-the-satsuma-garden&#34;&gt;Sengan-en, the Satsuma Garden&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After returning to Kagoshima from Yakushima late in the evening, I spent some time organizing my wet clothes and shoes.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The next morning, I had only about half a day to explore Kagoshima for the last time.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Even within that short span, I had a few places to visit: Shiroyama Observatory, Sengan-en, and Sakurajima.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Craving a peaceful morning walk, I decided to head to &lt;strong&gt;Sengan-en&lt;/strong&gt; first.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lush and Verdant Ancient Forests of Yakushima</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/1-yakushima/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/jr-travel/1-yakushima/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;journey-to-yakushima&#34;&gt;Journey to Yakushima&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On the first day of my trip, I took a morning flight to Fukuoka, exchanged my physical JR Pass, and stayed in Fukuoka for the day.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;The plan was to activate the JR Pass on the second day to maximize its use.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;So, in a way, my first day wasn’t about heading straight to Yakushima but rather a &lt;strong&gt;preview of Fukuoka&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Hakata Station&#34; src=&#34;https://nmin11.github.io/jr-travel/yakushima-1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;During the day, I did some light shopping around Hakata Station and enjoyed Fukuoka’s nightlife, exploring Canal City and Nakasu in the evening.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
