<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Loko</title>
    <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Loko</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Major GC Algorithms</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/4-major-gc-algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/4-major-gc-algorithms/</guid>
      <description>This article was written with the intention of studying major GC algorithms more deeply while participating in the &amp;lsquo;Optimizing Java&amp;rsquo; study.
Serial GC The simplest GC implementation Only one thread performs GC after Stop-The-World (STW) Uses the mark-sweep-compact algorithm Not suitable for multi-threaded environments ❖ Enable Serial GC flag
java -XX:+UseSerialGC Parallel GC Default GC from Java 5 to 8 Also known as the Throughput Collector as it maximizes GC throughput Advantageous algorithm when there is sufficient memory space and a high number of cores Flags can be used to configure parameters such as the maximum number of threads, maximum pause time, and GC execution time ratio -XX:ParallelGCThreads=&amp;lt;N&amp;gt; -XX:MaxGCPauseMillis=&amp;lt;N&amp;gt; -XX:GCTimeRatio=&amp;lt;N&amp;gt; ❖ Enable Parallel GC flag</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS CDK is not a silver bullet</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/3-aws-cdk-is-not-a-silver-bullet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/3-aws-cdk-is-not-a-silver-bullet/</guid>
      <description>TL;DR (Generated by Notion AI) While AWS CDK (Cloud Development Kit) has become a popular choice for infrastructure-as-code (IaC) development, it is important to note that it is not a silver bullet solution for all use cases.
Firstly, AWS CDK may not be the best choice for smaller projects or simple infrastructure setups that do not require a lot of customization. In such cases, using a simpler IaC tool or even writing code directly in the AWS console may be more efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mysterious S3 Access Denied Error</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/2-s3-access-denied-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/2-s3-access-denied-error/</guid>
      <description>How I discovered the error I actually encountered the same error twice.
Neither error occurred in the course of work, but both occurred on the side projects that I had implemented a feature to test work-related functionality.
What I implemented was a Lambda function that triggered by S3 object created event.
These Lambda functions had a common logic: get the object&amp;rsquo;s key name from the received event, and look up the object information again via that key name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make tech blog with Github Pages</title>
      <link>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/1-make-tech-blog-with-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nmin11.github.io/en/blog/1-make-tech-blog-with-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>0. What is Github Pages? Github Pages is a useful tool that allows us to create our own website for free without a server or DB.
It is widely used not only for blogs but also for resumes, portfolios, official documents, galleries, and archives.
(Especially, many developer create portfolio with Github Pages.)
I also chose Github Pages because I wanted to create a new tech blog!
Github Pages 1. Why Hugo?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
